{
    "subject": "resource/Kauai_King",
    "predicate": "property/fmf",
    "object": "resource/Discovery_(horse)",
    "human_readable": "Kauai King fathered Discovery (horse).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8385471701622009,
            "question": "Who is the father of Discovery (horse)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5785537958145142,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Kauai King and Discovery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5663475394248962,
            "question": "Where was Discovery (horse) born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5384467244148254,
            "question": "Is Kauai King a horse breeder?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5108968615531921,
            "question": "What is Kauai King known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4829215407371521,
            "question": "What breed of horse is Discovery?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48243018984794617,
            "question": "When was Discovery (horse) born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3411158323287964,
            "question": "What is the name of the horse's father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2960541844367981,
            "question": "What achievements did Discovery (horse) accomplish during its life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1726972460746765,
            "question": "Does Discovery have any famous offspring?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kauai King fathered Discovery (horse).",
            "html": "dbpedia_4796_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What achievements did Discovery (horse) accomplish during its life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4796_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the horse's father?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4796_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was Discovery (horse) born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4796_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4796_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me know if you have other triples to evaluate! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that there is no mention in the documents about a person named \"Discovery\" being a horse or related to Kauai's King. The document does mention Kauai's nickname as \"Hawaii\u2019s Island of Discovery\", but it refers to the island itself, not a person or animal."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context provided does not mention any king of Kauai who fathered a discovery related to horses. The information in the documents is about historical figures like Captain James Cook, King Kaumuali\u02bbi, and events such as the unification of Hawaiian Islands under King Kamehameha I's rule. There is no reference to a \"Discovery\" horse or any king fathering a discovery related to horses."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}